codeclimate.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy - Code Climate

Last revised on June 26, 2011

**In addition to this Privacy Policy, Code Climate also hasTerms of Service.**

    Code Climate Inc
    PO Box 1145
    New York, NY 10159

### The Gist

Code Climate Inc will collect certain non-personally identify information about you as you use our sites. We may use this data to better understand our users. We can also publish this data, but the data will be about a large group of users, not individuals.

We will also ask you to provide personal information, but you'll always be able to opt out. If you give us personal information, we won't do anything evil with it.

We can also use cookies, but you can choose not to store these.

That's the basic idea, but you must read through the entire Privacy Policy below and agree with all the details before you use any of our sites.

### Reuse

This document is based upon the [Automattic Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and is licensed under [Creative Commons Attribution Share-Alike License 2.5](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/). Basically, this means you can use it verbatim or edited, but you must release new versions under the same license and you have to credit Automattic somewhere (like this!). Automattic is not connected with and does not sponsor or endorse Code Climate Inc or its use of the work.

Code Climate Inc ("Code Climate") makes available services include our web sites (http://codeclimate.com/), our blog, our API, and any other software, sites, and services offered by Code Climate Inc in connection to any of those (taken together, the "Service"). It is Code Climate Inc's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Questions

If you have question about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at hello@codeclimate.com

### Visitors

Like most website operators, Code Climate Inc collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Code Climate Inc's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Code Climate Inc's visitors use its website. From time to time, Code Climate Inc may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Code Climate Inc also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Code Climate Inc does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. We may also collect and use IP addresses to block users who violated our Terms of Service.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Code Climate Inc's websites choose to interact with Code Climate Inc in ways that require Code Climate Inc to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Code Climate Inc gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Code Climate Inc collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Code Climate Inc. Code Climate Inc does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Service-related activities.

Additionally, some interactions, such as posting a comment, may ask for optional personal information. For instance, when posting a comment, may provide a website that will be displayed along with a user's name when the comment is displayed. Supplying such personal information is completely optional and is only displayed for the benefit and the convenience of the user.

### Aggregated Statistics

Code Climate Inc may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to the Service. For instance, Code Climate Inc may monitor the most popular parts of the http://codeclimate.com/. Code Climate Inc may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Code Climate Inc does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Code Climate Inc discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Code Climate Inc's behalf or to provide services available at Code Climate Inc's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Service, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Code Climate Inc will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Code Climate Inc discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Code Climate Inc believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Code Climate Inc, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Service and have supplied your email address, Code Climate Inc may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Code Climate Inc and our products. We primarily use our website and blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Code Climate Inc takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the Service each time the visitor returns. Code Climate Inc uses cookies to help Code Climate Inc identify and track visitors, their usage of Code Climate Inc Service, and their Service access preferences. Code Climate Inc visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Code Climate Inc's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Code Climate Inc's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Data Storage

Code Climate Inc uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Service. You understand that although you retain full rights to your data, it may be stored on third party storage and transmitted through third party networks.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Code Climate Inc may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Code Climate Inc's sole discretion. Code Climate Inc encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
